constants={
}
constants.questionaireLevelOne=[
  {
    question:"What is Flash's power?",
    options:["Flight","Invisibility","Speed","None"],
    answer:"c"
  },
  {
    question:"What is Batman's name?",
    options:["Bruce Wayne","Clark Kent","Barry Allen","Louis Lane"],
    answer:"a"
  },
  {
    question:"What is Superman's dad's name?",
    options:["Orlando","Clark Kent","Jor-El","Jack Kent"],
    answer:"c"
  },
  {
    question:"What is the true identity of the Batgirl we know best?",
    options:["Dick Grayson","Barbara Gordon","Talia al Ghul","Louis Lane"],
    answer:"b"
  },
  {
    question:"How did the original Flash get his powers?",
    options:["Gamma radiation","Inhaled nuclear fumes","Caught in a space/time warp","Stuck in ice for 100 years"],
    answer:"b"
  }
]


constants.questionaireLevelTwo=[
  {
    question:"In 'Batman v Superman,' Diana Prince and Bruce Wayne meet while gazing at what ancient weapon?",
    options:["Staff of Amun-Ra","Sword of Alexander the Great","Seven-Branched Sword","None"],
    answer:"b"
  },
  {
    question:"Where does Barry Allen keep his 'Flash' costume?",
    options:["Ring","Wallet","Bag","Under Clothes"],
    answer:"a"
  },
  {
    question:"What supervillain below is not a member of the 'Suicide Squad'?",
    options:["Cap Boomerang","DeadShot","Harley Quinn","The Joker"],
    answer:"d"
  },
  {
    question:"The face of the supervillain Darkseid was inspired by this famous actor:",
    options:["Israeli Alon Abutbul","American Jack Palance","Australian Peter Finch","Canadian Leslie Nielsen"],
    answer:"b"
  },
  {
    question:"What DC Comics supervillain has Mark Hamill not voiced?",
    options:["Solomon Grundy","The Joker","Sinestro","Darkseid"],
    answer:"d"
  }
]

module.exports=constants;
